{
    "id": "f47c8dbec3964bd1818d01c83a97cbea",
    "title": "Another, Other And Others",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "71140cf531d243e68b7acbaa822e4ec2",
            "title": "Another, Other And Others",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He has bought ............................... home.",
                    "description": "Another means an extra.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where are the ......................................?",
                    "description": "Others is the plural form of other. It is normally used alone without a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Show me the ....................................... hand?",
                    "description": "Before a noun other has no plural form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can I have ................................... cup of coffee?",
                    "description": "Another means an extra.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We must love one .....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The two brothers love each .................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can't find the ...................................... photos.",
                    "description": "Before a noun other has no plural form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Raju has arrived but the ........................................ haven't.",
                    "description": "Others is the plural form of other. It is normally used alone without a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You won't get ....................................... chance.",
                    "description": "Another means an extra.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "others"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you have any ........................................ colors?",
                    "description": "Other is similar to different.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can take this. I will take the ................................... one.",
                    "description": "Other is similar to different.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You should water the plants every ......................................... day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "others",
                        "another"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}